ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Unions Face Dual Fight in the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 62)
  Morning Advocate. September 1, 1977
- Stevens Ruled in Contempt For Antiunion Activities, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 63)
  the Denver Post. September 1, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Held in Contempt by Federal Appeals Court as 'Notorious Recidivist', 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 64)
    Service Union Reporter. September 1977
  - Item 2: Labor Investigation, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 64)
    Texas Catholic Herald. November 18, 1977
  - Item 3: Labor Film, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 64)
    The Herald Statesman. November 26, 1977
- Union Exec Says Stevens Ruling Is A 'First', 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 65)
  The Charlotte Observer. September 3, 1977
- Labor, Management Agree: A Revision of Labor Laws Could Transform South, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 66)
  September 6, 1977.
- Full Employment Week, Sept. 4-10, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 67)
  Labor News. September 1, 1977
- The Hot Battle Over Labor Law Reform, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 68)
  Forbes. September 1, 1977
- Stevens Co. Ruled in Contempt of Court, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 69)
  The Washington Star. September 1, 1977
- Court Flays Stevens Textile Firm For Violating Employees' Rights, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 70)
  The Washington Post. September 1, 1977
- Anti-Union Activities Cited: 2nd Circuit Finds Major Textile Firm in Contempt, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 71)
  Law Bulletin. September 1, 1977
- Appeal Court Slaps Textile Firm For Violating Rights of Workers, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 72)
  The Miami Herald. September 2, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Co. Found In Contempt of Court, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 73)
  Philadelphia Daily News. September 2, 1977
- Six Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Contract Said Nearer After Ruling, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 74)
    The News and Observer. September 2, 1977
  - Item 2: Textile Scofflaw Brought to Bay, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Item 3: Textile Union, J. P. Stevens Still At Odds, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Item 4: Court Says J. P. Stevens Violated Workers' Rights, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 74)
    The News and Observer. September 1, 1977
  - Item 5: Court Cites Stevens Co. For Contempt, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 74)
    Daily Herald. September 1, 1977
  - Item 6: Court Orders Stevens To Halt Antiunionism, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 74)
    Durham Morning Herald. September 1, 1977
- Civic Center at Roanoke Rapids, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 75)
  Union Reporter. September 1977
- Stevens To Ask High Court Review, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 76)
  Durham Herald. September 3, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Will Seek Reversal By Supreme Court, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 77)
  The News and Observer. September 3, 1977
- Unions Knocking On Sunbelt's Door, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 78)
  The Atlanta Journal. September 4, 1977
- Labor Battles In The South, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 79)
  The Atlanta Journal and The Atlanta Constitution. September 4, 1977
- Federal Appeals Court Rules Stevens In Contempt, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 80)
  Union Advocate. September 5, 1977
- Stevens and the Law, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 81)
  Greensboro Daily News. September 7, 1977
- Executive Suite's Viewpoint: Says Unions No 'Blessing' and Need No New Legal Powers, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 82)
  October 7, 1977.
- In Stevens-Union Battle, Distortion, Fear Abound, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 83)
  The Sunday Bulletin. September 11, 1977
- N.C. Town May Be Loser in Labor Struggle, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 84)
  The Flint Journal. September 11, 1977
- Labor and the Law, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 85)
  Enterprise. September 15, 1977
- Stevens Policies Draw Heavy Fire, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 86)
  Labor News. September 16, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Workers Gain World Support, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 87)
  San Diego Labor Leader. September 22, 1977
- Labor Law Reform Foes Try to Muster Forces, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 88)
  Daily News Record. September 29, 1977
- Unions Create Massive Unemployment, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 89)
  The Minneapolis Daily American. September 30, 1977
- Convention Hits Scofflaw Employers, Urges Congress Reform Labor Law, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 90)
  TWU Express. October 1977
- ACTWU vs. J. P. Stevens and Co., 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 91)
- J. P. Stevens vs. Textile Union: A Showdown Nears, News clipping (Box 3, Folder 92)
- J. P. Stevens Workers Gain World Support, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 93)
  Northwest Illinois Labor News. October 1977
- Baptist Clergyman Asks Action Against Anti-Unionism in South, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 94)
  Zions Herald. October 1977
- The Voices of Business, 1977; News clipping (Box 3, Folder 95)
  Journal of Commerce Review. October 5, 1977
- GOP Loses First Round To Halt House Passage Of Union Bill, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Nashville Banner. October 5, 1977
- Workers Never Recover From Union Boycotts, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Four copies of the same article published in the Mount Greenwood Express, the Bremen Messenger, and the Palos Park Citizen. October 6, 1977
- Missions From Moscow: Soviet Banker and 'Labor Leaders' Cheered and Feted in New York, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Inside Labor press release by Victor Riesel. October 6, 1977
- Reform Bill Inspired By Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Greenville News. October 7, 1977
- Local 67, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Racine Labor. October 7, 1977
- Labor Group Aims To Upgrade Standards For Women Workers, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 6)
  The Pittsburgh Press. October 8, 1977
- NY Priest Here To Push Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 7)
  The Cincinnati Enquirer. October 11, 1977
- Working For J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Chicago Sum-Times. October 9,. 1977
- Stevens Employees Fight Against Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Greenville Piedmont. October 10, 1977
- Committee Hears Strong Case for Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Michigan AFL-CIO News. October 13, 1977
- Stevens Charged In Union-Busting, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Danbury News-Times. October 14, 1977
- Two Articles from the Westerly Sun and the New York Teacher, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Earnings Take Dive, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Nw York Teacher. September 18, 1977
  - Item 2: Flood Backs Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Westerly Sun. October 17, 1977
- Rhode Island AFL-CIO Asks Boycott of Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 13)
  The Providence Journal. October 18, 1977
- Growing Acceptance for the Coalition of Union Women, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 14)
  The New York Times. October 20, 1977
- Labor Board Backs Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 15)
  New Milford Times. October 20, 1977
- Wage Figures Paint A Distorted Picture, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 16)
  The Charlotte Observer. October 23, 1977
- Church/Labor Conference Set, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Portland Observer. October 20, 1977
- ACTWU Denies Workers Resist Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Daily News Record. October 20, 1977
- Panel Eyes Church-Labor Ties, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Oregon Labor Press. October 21, 1977
- Don't Sleep With Stevens' Activists Battle Textile Giant With Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 20)
  St. Louis Post-Dispatch. October 24, 1977
- The Law Is The Law, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Valley Times-News. October 25, 1977
- Priest Censures Textile Firm, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 22)
  San Francisco Examiner. October 29, 1977
- Talk Due On Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Ithaca Journal. October 31, 1977
- The Boycott of J. P. Stevens Products Comes to Bradlees, News clipping (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Stevens to Face Labor Complaints, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Danbury News-Times. November 11, 1977
- Call Renewed For Boycott of Textile Firms Products: J. P. Stevens Ruthlessly Continues Unfair Labor Practices in Its Plants, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 26)
  UA Journal. November 1977
- Union Boycott of Company Hurts Thousands of Workers, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Nation's Business. November 1977
- A Labor Victory, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Progressive. November 1977
- Performers at Rally for Stevens Workers, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Frontpage. November 1977
- Countervailing Duties Sought by ACTW, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Union Supporters Suing Chamber, City, County, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Lauringburg Exchange. November 2, 1977
- Suit Attacks Laurinburg Funds, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 32)
  The Fayetteville Observer. November 2, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Troubles, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 33)
  The Citizen Register. November 2, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Troubles, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 34)
  The Reporter Dispatch. November 2, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Organizer Condemns Injustice Within J. P. Stevens' Operations, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Cornell Sun. November 3, 1977
  - Item 2: Baptist Clergyman Asks Action Against Anti-Unionism in South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Gospel Herald. October 18, 1977
  - Item 3: Catholic Charities Unit Endorses National Boycott of Stevens Co., 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Zion's Herald. October 1977
- ACTWU Files Civil Lawsuit Calling For Removal of JPS Directors, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Roanoke Rapids Herald. November 3, 1977
- Two Articles from the San Diego Labor Leader and the Catholic Sentinel, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: If You Can't Take the Hear Try Obeying the Law, J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 37)
    San Diego Labor Leader. November 3, 1977
  - Item 2: Economic Matters Said Church Concern, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Catholic Sentinel. November 4. 1977
- Haskell Smith: A Millhand Views Retirement, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 38)
  The Atlanta Journal and The Atlanta Constitution. November 13, 1977
- Textile Workers Sue J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 39)
  The Washington Star. November 10, 1977
- Stevens the Target; 14b the Culprit, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Dayton Daily News. November 11, 1977
- Unions War On Stevens With 2 Suits, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 41)
  The Charlotte Observer. November 11, 1977
- Plot Seen to Keep Unions Out of the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 42)
  The Citizen Register. November 11, 1977
- Union Brings an Antitrust Suit Against Stevens Textile Firm, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 43)
  The Washington Post. November 11, 1977
- Plot Seen to Keep Unions Out of the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 44)
  The Daily Argus. November 11, 1977
- Cornell Speech: Union Executive Discusses 'World' Boycott of Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 45)
  The Ithaca Journal. November 3, 1977
- It Was Friendly Little Tarheel Town, Then Industry, Union Began Struggle, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 46)
  November 2, 1977.
- Plot Seen to Keep Unions Out of the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 47)
  The Daily Times. November 11, 1977
- Meany Supports Suit Against Textile Firm, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 48)
  The Detroit News. November 11, 1977
- Plot Seen to Keep Unions Out of the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 49)
  The Daily Item. November 11, 1977
- Stevens Sued By Textile Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 50)
  Elizabeth City Advance. November 11, 1977
- Union Charges Conspiracy, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 51)
  Herald Examiner. November 11, 1977
- Plot Seen to Keep Unions Out of the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 52)
  The Herald Statesman. November 11, 1977
- Meany Endorses Suit Accusing Company of 'Union-Busting', 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 53)
  The Miami Herald. November 11, 1977
- Textile Union Sues Stevens Over Labor Freeze in South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 54)
  The Miami News. November 11, 1977
- Union Alleges Stevens 'Plot', 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 55)
  The News and Observer. November 11, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Faces Stiff Contempt Fine, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 56)
  Quincy Labor News. November 11, 1977
- Federal Court Lowers The Boom With Warning To J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 57)
  Indianapolis Leader. November 11, 1977
- Organizing, Imports Chief Issues At Industrial Union Convention, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Union Sues J. P. Stevens, Charges Plot, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 59)
  Herald American. November 11, 1977
- Two Articles from the Gastonia Gazette and the Wilmington Star, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Stevens: Textile Union's Suits 'Frivolous', 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Gastonia Gazette. November 11, 1977
  - Item 2: Unions File Suit, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Wilmington Star. November 14, 1977
- Plot Seen to Keep Unions Out of the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 61)
  The Reporter Dispatch. November 11, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Boycott Is Endorsed, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 62)
  The Charlotte Observer. November 12, 1977
- Stevens Calls Suits By Union Frivolous, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 63)
  Columbia State. November 12, 1977
- Conspiracy Role Laid to Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 64)
  The Atlanta Journal. November 10, 1977
- Federal Court Lowers The Boom With Warning To J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 65)
  Galesburg Labor News. November 10, 1977
- Two Articles from The Providence Journal and the Nichi Bei Times, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Poor Political Judgment, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 66)
    The Providence Journal. November 23, 1977
  - Item 2: Japanese to Boycott U.S. Firm's Products, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 66)
    Nichi Bei Times. November 9, 1977
- A Open Letter to the Citizens of Rhea and Roane Counties, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 67)
  November 10, 1977.
- Union Busting At J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 68)
  Valley Advocate. November 9, 1977
- The Organizer: This Priest Has A Union Mission, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 69)
  The Charlotte Observer. November 6, 1977
- Textile Giant Faces Stiff Penalties: Federal Court Lowers The Boom With Warning To J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 70)
  St. Louis Labor Tribune. November 10, 1977
- Church Has Union Role, Says Priest, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 71)
  The Seattle Daily Times. November 10, 1977
- Textile Giant Faces Stiff Penalties: Federal Court Lowers The Boom With Warning To J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 72)
  Southern Illinois Labor Tribune. November 3, 1977
- Textile Workers' Suit Adds to Stevens' Woes, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 73)
  California Apparel News. November 4, 1977
- Unionizing In Mills Anguishes Pastors, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Boycott Aimed At J. P. Stevens Employment Policies, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 75)
  Republican Eagle. November 8, 1977
- Corporate Arrogance, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 76)
  The Record. November 9, 1977
- Union Doesn't Want Pact: J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 77)
  The Detroit News. November 9, 1977
- Two Articles from the Daily News Record, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Stevens Warns Congress on Labor Bill, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 78)
    Daily News Record. November 9, 1977
  - Item 2: ACTW Files Suit Against NC Officials, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Real Culprits Are The Boycotters, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 79)
  Odessa American. November 14, 1977
- Anti-Union Drive Uses Tax Money, Suit Claims, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 80)
  The News and Observere. November 13, 1977
- Council of Churches Backs Union Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 81)
  The Christian Science Monitor. November 14, 1977
- Textile Boycott Backed By Local Labor Council, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 82)
  The Daily Mercury. November 14, 1977
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Japanese Join Stevens Curb, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 83)
    Chicago Daily News. November 12, 1977
  - Item 2: Stevens Workers Hold Anti-Union Session, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 83)
    Florence News. November 14, 1977
  - Item 3: In its continuing battle to unionize J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 83)
    Chemical Weekly. November 16, 1977
- Five Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Gov. Garrahy Endorses Boycott of J. P. Stevens Textile Goods, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 84)
    The Providence Journal. November 17, 1977
  - Item 2: Stevens Replies, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 84)
    The Greenboro Record. November 15, 1977
  - Item 3: Union Rep To Explain Anti-J. P. Stevens Move, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 84)
    Republican Eagle. November 4, 1977
  - Item 4: Churches Join Stevens Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 84)
    The Charlotte News. November 15, 1977
  - Item 5: Group Hears Boycott Talk, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 84)
    Harvard Crimson. October 27, 1977
- Four Articles from various newspapers., 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Labor Film, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 85)
    The Daily Argus. November 26, 1977
  - Item 2: Labor Film, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 85)
    The Reporter Dispatch. November 26, 1977
  - Item 3: Labor Film, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 85)
    The Standard-Star. November 26, 1977
  - Item 4: NEAJ Congress Supports Stevens Company Boycott, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 85)
    Jewish Advocate. November 17, 1977
- NLRB Office Dismisses Most JPS Milledgeville Charges, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 86)
  Roanoke Rapids Herald. November 18, 1977
- Church Aid to Labor Urged, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 87)
  The News and Observer. November 20, 1977
- Critics Take Aim at Supreme Court Historical Group, News clipping (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Profile of Barbara Merrill, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 89)
  New Crusader. November 19, 1977
- Stevens Is Target of Rally, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 90)
  The Charlotte Observer. November 21, 1977
- ACTW Rally Makes Appeal to Workers At Stevens' Plants, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 91)
  Daily News Record. November 21, 1977
- Most Charges Against Georgia Plant Dropped, Says Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 92)
  Laurens Advertiser. November 21, 1977
- J. P. Stevens Company Workers Rally In Support Of Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 93)
  Spartenburg Herald. November 21, 1977
- Rally Climaxes Weekend of ACTWU, JPS Activitiy, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 94)
  Daily Herald. November 21, 1977
- Stevens Workers Gather In Support of Textile Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 95)
  Greenville News. November 21,1977
- Rally Steps Up Union's Battle Against Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 96)
- Union Opens Local Office, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 97)
  Greenville Piedmont. November 21,1977
- Union Official Vows To Stay In Stevens Fight, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 98)
  The Charlotte News. November 21, 1977
- Petition Calls For Union Decertification Vote, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 99)
  Roanoke Rapids Herald. November 20, 1977
- Charges Dismissed In Stevens Case, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 100)
  Shelby Star. November 19, 1977
- Labor Bill and Union Boycott Imperil Workers' Rights, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 101)
  Wallace Enterprise. November 17, 1977
- Selling the Union To the U.S. Textile Workers: Getting a Foot In the Door, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 102)
  Financial Times. November 22, 1977
- New Twists, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 103)
  Belton News. November 23, 1977
- A 'Christian' Gesture?, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 104)
  Anderson Independent. November 23, 1977
- Poor Political Judgment, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 105)
  The Evening Bulletin. November 23, 1977
- Bishops, Church Council 'Converging' On Issues, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 106)
  Catholic Sun. November 23, 1977
- Steven Says Union's Suits Are Frivolous and Lacking In Merit, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 107)
  Bolivar Bulletin-Times. November 24, 1977
- Five Articles from various newspapers, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: J. P. Stevens Faces Labor Trial, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 108)
    The Atlanta Journal. November 25, 1977
  - Item 2: The Amalgamated Clothing and Textiles Workers Union has asked a federal court, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 108)
    The Dillon Herald. November 10, 1977
  - Item 3: Labor Film, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 108)
    The Daily Times. November 26, 1977
  - Item 4: Labor Film, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 108)
    The Citizen Register. November 26, 1977
  - Item 5: Labor Film, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 108)
    The Tarrytown News. November 26, 1977
- Stevens Dispute To Affect Area?, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 109)
  Catholic Northwest Progress. November 25, 1977
- 50 Units Represented: Rally Vows to Sign All Stevens Plants, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 110)
  AFL-CIO News. November 26, 1977
- CBS Documentary Views the Textile Industry and Ministry in the South, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 111)
  North Carolina Catholic. November 27, 1977
- A Town Divided, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 112)
  St. Louis Post-Dispatch. November 29, 1977
- ACTWU Seeks Justification, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 113)
  Calumet. November 29, 1977
- Proposed Law Would Cripple Negotiations, Stevens Says, 1977; News clipping (Box 4, Folder 114)
  News and Record. November 15, 1977
- Editor Fears Labor Strife in South, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Winston-Salem Sentinel. December 1, 1977
- Textile Workers Fight On: The Battle Against J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Ms. December 1, 1977
- Vote Would Help In Stevens Case, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Cheraw Chronicle. December 1, 1977
- Local Programming., 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 4)
  St. Cloud Visitor. December 1, 1977
- Ministers Support Textile Union, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 5)
- The Unions' Best Friend, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 6)
  The Boston Globe. December 6, 1977
- Union Opens Boycott of Stevens Textiles, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Newsday. December 7, 1977
- Union Launches Boycott Of Stevens In 27 Cities, 1976; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 8)
  The Charlotte Observer. December 7, 1977
- Workers Gather In Massive Rally Against J. P. Stevens, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 9)
  The Los Angeles Citizen. December 9, 1977
- Women in 'Labor' Bear New Fruits, 1977; News clipping (Box 5, Folder 10)